ELLIOTT LOCKWOOD

Austin, TX 78704
(713) 562 – 6480 | lockwood721@gmail.com
www.github.com/elock721| elliottjlockwood@herokuapp.com
www.linkedin.com/in/elliottjlockwood

SUMMARY

Recent full stack bootcamp grad with a 4-year bachelor's degree and background in oil and gas. Always referred to by coworkers as a hardworking, adaptable, exceptional team player. Effective at approaching every job task or challenge with a combination of creativity and my passion for problem solving.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Front End: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, ReactJS, Handlebars.js

Back End: Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, Express

WEB DEV PROJECTS

*To be completed | Link to GitHub | Link to Deployed Project

- Short summary of project (1-2 lines)
- Your core responsibilities in project (1-2 lines)
- Tools / languages used

*To be completed | Link to GitHub | Link to Deployed Project

- Short summary of project (1-2 lines)
- Your core responsibilities in project (1-2 lines)
- Tools / languages used

Fish Guide Friend | https://github.com/elock721/Fish-Guide-Friend

June 2020

- Allows you to find the highest rated fishing guides in a specific area
- UI Engineer responsible for creating user friendly interface
- HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, jQuery, JSON, AJAX, APIs

EXPERIENCE

Floor Hand (Contract) Spencer Ogden

07**/**2016 – 04/2020

 Member of the drilling team responsible for all necessary drilling operations on board vessel. Tasks included safe execution of BHA assembly/deconstruction, proper alignment of choke & kill manifold, and reliable assistance to the drilling fluid engineer.

Floor Hand Ensco Offshore

10**/**2013 – 06/2016

 Member of the drilling team responsible for all necessary drilling operations on board vessel. Tasks included safe execution of BHA assembly/deconstruction, proper alignment of choke & kill manifold, and reliable assistance to the drilling fluid engineer. Roustabout 08/2012 – 10/2013 Hercules Offshore

 Member of the deck management team responsible for the organization of the vessel's cargo and deck space. Tasks included banksman ship for crane operator and efficient coordination with other departments on board to execute necessary cargo lifts.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate: Univ. of Texas, Austin, TX 2020

Bachelor of General Studies in History: Univ. of Kansas, Lawrence, KS 2012